// "_id": "66caddd80ee33af8175949f3",
//             "Question": "What is TDZ.",
//             "Type": "Objective",
//             "Answer": "4",
//             "Choice1": "Hoisting",
//             "Choice2": "Scope",
//             "Choice3": "Promise",
//             "Choice4": "None on the above",
//             "createBy": "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
//             "createdAt": "2024-08-25T07:31:36.101Z",
//             "updatedAt": "2024-08-25T07:31:36.101Z",
//             "__v": 0
export interface AssessmentQuestion {
  Question: string;
  Choice1: string;
  Choice2: string;
  Choice3?: string;
  Choice4?: string;
  Answer: string;
  Type: string;
  quizSetId?: string;
  imgUrl?: string;
  createBy: string;
  createdAt: string;
  updatedAt: string;
  _id: string;
  __v: number;
}

export type AssessmentQuestionKey = keyof typeof AssessmentQuestions;

export const AssessmentQuestions: AssessmentQuestion[] = [
  {
    _id: "66caddd80ee33af8175949f3",
    Question: "What is TDZ.",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "4",
    Choice1: "Hoisting",
    Choice2: "Scope",
    Choice3: "Promise",
    Choice4: "None on the above",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:31:36.101Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:31:36.101Z",
    __v: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadd420ee33af8175949ea",
    Question: "What is React?",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "4",
    Choice1: "Library",
    Choice2: "Framework",
    Choice3: "Language",
    Choice4: "Compiler",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:29:06.898Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:29:06.898Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949ee",
    Question: "What is Html?",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "4",
    Choice1: "Library",
    Choice2: "Framework",
    Choice3: "Language",
    Choice4: "Compiler",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949ef",
    Question: "Semantic Tags",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "2",
    Choice1: "Div",
    Choice2: "span",
    Choice3: "main",
    Choice4: "br",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.389Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.389Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949ed",
    Question: "What is React?",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "4",
    Choice1: "Library",
    Choice2: "Framework",
    Choice3: "Language",
    Choice4: "Compiler",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949ec",
    Question: "What is Html?",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "4",
    Choice1: "Library",
    Choice2: "Framework",
    Choice3: "Language",
    Choice4: "Compiler",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949eb",
    Question: "Semantic Tags",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "2",
    Choice1: "Div",
    Choice2: "span",
    Choice3: "main",
    Choice4: "br",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949e9",
    Question: "What is Html?",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "4",
    Choice1: "Library",
    Choice2: "Framework",
    Choice3: "Language",
    Choice4: "Compiler",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949ea",
    Question: "Semantic Tags",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "2",
    Choice1: "Div",
    Choice2: "span",
    Choice3: "main",
    Choice4: "br",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
  },
  {
    _id: "66cadda50ee33af8175949e8",
    Question: "What is Html?",
    Type: "Objective",
    Answer: "4",
    Choice1: "Library",
    Choice2: "Framework",
    Choice3: "Language",
    Choice4: "Compiler",
    createBy: "66c98bb660b46e67f1e30496",
    __v: 0,
    createdAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
    updatedAt: "2024-08-25T07:30:45.388Z",
  },
];
